On the other hand, your casual clothes look fresh.
私服が逆に新鮮ですね
I don't really post anything on SNS.
あんまり、あんまりっていうか、まずSNSにあげてないです
Right.
よね
However, as promised, you contacted me,
しか も、約束通りというか、連絡いただいて、
It's still cute.
相変わらず可愛いですね
Is this how you usually feel?
結構普段はこういう感じですか?
In terms of clothes.
服装的には
It's like this.
こんな感じですね
Last time, it felt like I was suddenly cosplaying,
なんか前回は、いきなりコスプレって感じだったんですけど、
That's why I wasn't wearing any underwear.
だから下着もつけてなかったですよね
Today is normal, and inside is also pretty normal.
今日は普通に、内側も結構普通というか、
As usual.
普段通り
Wait, let's take a shower together...
ちょっと、せっかくなんで、一緒にシャワーというか、
Don't you want to take a bath?
お風呂入りません?
yes.
はい
It's not often that I take a bath with my followers.
フォロワーさんとお風呂入るってことはあんまないですよね
Is this underwear right below?
この下ってすぐ下着ですか?
Can I open it for you?
開いてみせてもらっていいですか?
Does the bottom match as well?
下もお揃いって感じ?
Can I have the mistake below?
下のミスでもらっていいですか?
Shall I take off my top too?
上も脱ぎましょうか
can?
できる?
Well then, let's go take a bath.
じゃあ、ちょっとお風呂行きましょうか
Can I put it on first?
先に着てもらっていいですか?
Just put your back here.
ちょっとこっち背中つけて
Turn your back.
背中向けて
Ah, that...
あー、その...
Ah, the place where I keep getting stuck
あー、縁ずっとたまってるところ
but.
が
Lie behind her and spread your legs.
その 後ろに寝っ転がって足広げて
Good morning, good morning.
おはん、おはん
Good morning.
おはん
Good morning, good morning.
おはん、おはん